And I just want a million dollars!
而我只想要一百万美金
Rachel?
瑞秋
Oh, God, Monica! Hi! Thank God!
噢 老天爷 摩妮卡 感谢上帝
I went to your building and this guy with a hammer said...
我刚到你那里去 而你不在 那个拿着大锤子的家伙说...
...that you might be here, and you are.
你可能在这里 你真在这里
- Can I get you some coffee?  - Decaf.
- 你想喝点咖啡吗？- 无咖啡因的
Okay, everybody, this is Rachel, another Lincoln High survivor.
好了 各位 这位是瑞秋 另一个林肯高中的幸存者
This is everybody. This is Chandler and Phoebe...
这就是各位 这是钱德  菲比
...and Joey. And remember my brother, Ross?
乔伊  还有 你还记得我哥哥罗斯吗？
- Sure!  - Hey.
- 当然  - 嘿
- Hi.  - Oh, God.
- 嗨  - 天啊
So you wanna tell us now,
那你现在可以告诉我们了吗？
or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
还是说我们在等着四位湿漉的伴娘？
Oh, God! Well, it started about a half-hour before the wedding.
好吧 大概在婚礼前半个小时
I was in this room with all the presents...
我在礼物间里
...and I was looking at this gravy boat.
看着那个肉汁壶
This really gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.
那是个非常好看的肉汁壶
When all of a sudden... Sweet 'N Low?
然后 突然…有代糖吗？
I realized...
我发现…
...I was more turned on by this gravy boat than by Barry.
我对这个肉汁壶 比对巴瑞更有冲动
Then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me:
然后我吓呆了 然后这个想法突然出现在脑中:
How much Barry looks like Mr. Potato Head.
巴瑞看起来多像洋芋头先生啊
You know, I mean, I always knew he looked familiar, but...
我总是觉得他眼熟 但是…
Anyway, I just had to get out of there, and I started wondering:
总之 我必须离开那里 我在想:
"Why am I doing this?" And "Who am I doing this for?"
"我为什么这样做？我为谁这样做？"
Anyway, I just didn't know where to go, and I know you and I have drifted apart...
我不知道该去哪里 而且我知道我和你有点疏远了
...but you're the only person I know in the city.
但你是我这个城市里唯一认识的人
Who wasn't invited to the wedding.
而且没有受邀参加你的婚礼
Oh, I was kind of hoping that wouldn't be an issue.
噢 我希望你不会把它当一回事…